livingspaces.com 2019-06-18

# Privacy Policy

### This Policy describes how we treat personal information collected in stores and on the websites where it is located. It also applies to our mobile site and apps. This policy does not apply to other interactions you might have with us.

This Policy describes how we treat personal information collected in stores and on the websites where it is located. It also applies to our mobile site and apps. This policy does not apply to other interactions you might have with us.

### We collect information from and about you

We collect contact information. We collect your name and email address. We may also collect your mailing address and your phone number.

We collect payment information. We collect your credit card number and billing address if you make a purchase.

We collect information you submit or post. We collect information you submit, for example when you post a review. These reviews are posted publicly to our website.

We collect demographic information. We may collect age and gender. We may also collect preference information like your home style.

We collect usage and location information. We collect information about the browser you are using. We also look at what site you came from to get to us. We look at what site you go to when you leave us. We may collect location information.

We collect device and mobile information. We collect device identifiers and IP addresses. We may collect information about which websites you visit when you use our store WiFi. We collect information using GPS and WiFi technology.

### We collect information in different ways

We collect information directly from you. We collect information from you when you sign up for an account or buy a product. We also collect information if you register to get a catalog or participate in a promotion. We also collect information from you when you contact us.

We collect information from you passively. We use tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons. We do this on various platforms. This includes our websites and apps. It also includes emails and in-store WiFi. We collect information about users over time when you use this website. We may have third parties collect personal information this way. We may also collect information from our mobile app. Learn more about these tools and how you can control them, here.

We get information about you from third parties. For example, our business and marketing partners may give us information about you. Social media platforms may also give us information about you. Other Living Spaces customers may provide us with your contact information. For example, if they want to share their “wish list” with you.

### We combine information

We combine information that we have collected from different media. For example, we combine information we collect offline with information we collect online. We may also combine information from emails and WiFi. We also combine information we get from a third party with information we already have.

### We use information as disclosed and described here

We use information to respond to your requests or questions. For example, we might use your information to respond to your feedback or product reviews. We also use your information to notify you if you win a contest.

We use information to improve our products and services. We may use your information to make our websites and products better. We might use your information to customize your experience.

We use information for security purposes. We may use information to protect our company and our customers. We also use information to protect our websites and app.

We use information for marketing purposes. For example, we might provide you with information about new products and special offers. We might also use your information to serve you ads about products and offers. These might be third party offers or products we think you would find interesting.

We use information to communicate with you. For example, we will contact you about your orders. We may contact you about product reviews or other feedback you give us. We might also contact you about this Policy or our website Terms.

We may use push notifications on our mobile apps.

We use information as otherwise permitted by law or as we may notify you.

### We may share information with third parties

We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf. For example, we share information with vendors who send emails or catalogs for us. We also share information with the company that provides customer financing. We may also share information with companies that help run our websites. We also share information with our delivery partners.

We may share your information with our business and marketing partners. For example, we might share information with third parties that co-sponsor a promotion. We may also share information with third parties that help us with marketing. This may include social media platforms.

We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves. For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud. This might include fraud we think has happened during a contest or promotion. Or we may share your information if you are the winner of a contest or promotion with anyone who requests a winner’s list.

We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business. For example, if part of our business was sold, we may give our customer list as part of that transaction.

We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.

### You have certain choices about how we use your information

You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails and catalog mailings. To stop receiving our promotional emails, follow the instructions in any promotional message you get from us. To stop receiving our catalogs, visit our catalog opt-out page, here. Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still send you transactional messages. These include responses to your requests and questions.

You can control cookies and tracking tools. To learn how we use cookies and other tracking tools, and to read our Do Not Track policy, please click here.

You can control tools on your mobile devices. For example, you can turn off the GPS locator or push notifications on your phone.

### These sites and apps are not intended for children

Our sites and apps are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can email us at webhelp@livingspaces.com. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.” Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children's privacy on-line [here](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/topics/protecting-kids-online).

### We use standard security measures

The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites and apps will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords.

### We may link to other sites or apps or have thrid party services on our platforms we do not control

If you click on a link to a third party site, you will be taken to websites or platforms we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of that website or platform. Read the privacy policy of other websites and companies carefully. We are not responsible for these third party practices.

### Feel free to contact us if you have more questions

If you have any questions about this Policy or want to correct or update your information, please email us at webhelp@livingspaces.com. You can also write to us or call at:

Living Spaces Furniture

14501 Artesia Boulevard

La Mirada, CA 90638

Telephone: (877) 266-7300

### We may update this Policy

From time to time we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our sites and app. Please check our sites and apps periodically for updates.
